<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Goplant on Scott Stolarski's Portfolio</title><link>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/</link><description>Recent content in Goplant on Scott Stolarski's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Making Cool Graphs</title><link>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/makingcoolgraphs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/makingcoolgraphs/</guid><description>Plotting Data Note on the data The data being plotted was from a twenty four hour test that I setup in the previous post. It turned out to be a 72 hour test because I left it running by accident. This test was setup inside during a particularly cloudy week, data results may vary. The extra data turned out to be a huge help when looking at the correlations of the final lines.</description></item><item><title>Goplant's First Test</title><link>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/firsttest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/firsttest/</guid><description>With the Microcontrollers successfully making requests to the GoPlant API, it&amp;rsquo;s finally time to plug in all sensors and try collecting some data! It just so happened that the week I wanted to try this also happened to be the week it was forecasted to rain every day and my Microcontrollers are far from water proof. Therefore, I grabbed the duct tape, one of my indoor plants, and got to work.</description></item><item><title>Goplant Project Description</title><link>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/projectsummary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stolarskis.github.io/posts/goplant/projectsummary/</guid><description>What is Goplant? Goplant is a wireless plant monitoring system that utilizes a few technologies I&amp;rsquo;m interesting in learning!
What does Goplant do? Goplant operates by programming Microcontrollers to collect sensor measurements (insert image of microcontroller) and send that data to the Goplant application that is in charge of storing that data in a database. Connecting the Microcontrollers to the internet, in order to reach the Goplant App is super easy thanks to the builtin wifi module (insert picture of wifi logo on micro controller).</description></item></channel></rss>